THOMAS COLLINS

Boulder, Colorado, United States

thco8465@colorado.edu

linkedin.com/in/thomas-collins-2188b22ab

Summary

Finishing my last semester pursuing a BA in computer science specializing in software engineering. Additionally, I will finish with a philosophy minor that has help balanced my academic pursuit. I have experience with Vue, React, Node.js, C++, Python, and PostgreSQL from classes taken and personal projects undertaken. Currently, I'm progressing as an after-school instructor at KidzToPros, making sure the kids have fun while learning about simple programming skills through block coding. I believe my strengths lie in my positive, motivated, and balanced approach to learning computer science.

Experience

BAM! Instructor

Brains & Motion Education

Nov 2023 - Present (5 months)

Property Management Assistant

Davis Enterprises

May 2023 - Aug 2023 (4 months)

Over the summer, I assisted in the maintenance of properties including landscaping and cleanup. Additionally, I worked on organizing property details onto excel.

Education



University of Colorado Boulder

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science Aug 2019 - May 2024



University of Colorado Boulder

2019 - 2024

Skills

Node.js • Software Development • React.js • Python (Programming Language) • PostgreSQL • Agile Methodologies • Programming • C++ • Java • Go